我想着该给艾玛吃第一块饼干了
You know, I'm thinking about letting Emma have her first cookie.
第一块
Her first cookie?
她常吃饼干
She has cookies all the time.
我没喂过她饼干
I've never given her a cookie.
-你给她了  -没有
- Have you? - No.
另外
No. And for the record,
我也没从罐子里拿白糖给她
I've also never given her frosting from a can.
瑞秋  领养中心要我们交一份推荐信
Hey, Rach, the adoption agency needs letters of recommendation...
你愿意帮我们写一封吗
...and we wondered if you would write one for us?
当然愿意  这是我的荣幸
Of course. I would be honored.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们是不是疏忽了一个人
I think there's been an oversight.
乔伊  我们本想找你
We would have asked you.
但又觉得你可能没兴趣
We thought you wouldn't be interested.
我们觉得你可能
It's just that we don't think of you
不擅长跟文字打交道
as really being so much with the words.
很明显我们错了
Clearly, we were wrong.
对于你们二位
I got a lot of nice stuff
我有很多好话可写
to say about you guys, okay?
而且我也非常清楚你们多想要个小孩
I know how much you want to have a baby...
我很想帮你们
...and I would love to help you get one.
好吧  乔伊  你来写
You know what? Joey. Then we want you to do it.
谢谢  我想想怎么开头
Thank you. All right. Let me see how I'm gonna start.
亲爱的婴孩领养权决定人
"Dear Baby Adoption Decider People...."
迫不及待想看你写的推荐信
So excited about your letter.
-嘿  -嘿  菲比
- Hey. - Hey, Phoebe.
-你可真好看  -没错  是很美
- Wow, don't you look nice. - Yes, I do.
今天迈克和我庆祝一周年
Today's Mike and my one-year anniversary.
什么事情的周年
What's it the anniversary of?
第一次约会  第一次亲吻  第一次上床
Your first date, your first kiss, first time you had sex?
对
Yeah.
你们会去好地方隆重庆祝
So you must be going somewhere fancy to celebrate.
看尼克斯队篮球比赛
A Knicks game.
你不觉得自己穿得过于隆重了吗
Aren't you a little overdressed?
我从未和哪个男人有过一周年
I've never had a one-year anniversary before...
所以不管去哪里庆祝  我一定要盛装打扮
...so no matter where we go, I'm wearing something fancy...
戴最好的珠宝
...I'm gonna put on my finest jewelry...
还要在公共洗手间嘿咻
...and we're gonna have sex in a public restroom.
你们做过
You guys do that?
钱德勒连在我家洗手间嘿咻也不肯
Chandler won't even have sex in our bathroom.
洗手间是尿尿的地方
That's where people make number two.
我有点时间
So, you know, I have a little time
你想不想
if you want to....
好想  但是我要判卷子
I'd love to, but I really have to grade these papers.
好  那好吧
Fine. It's fine.
那我就自己去洗澡
I'll just shower by myself.
B...
你给陶器仓库的目录上也打了个B
You gave a B to a Pottery Barn catalog.
他们表现尚可
Well, it had some good ideas.
脱衣服吧
Take off your shirt.
-该死  -开门  瑞秋  你妹妹来了
- Damn it. - Rachel, open up! It's your sister!
我要跟你谈谈
I have to talk to you.
嗨  艾米.
Hi, Amy.
-你不是瑞秋  -牙尖嘴利
- You're not Rachel. - Still sharp as a tack.
查莉  这是瑞秋的妹妹艾米
Charlie, this is Rachel's sister Amy.
艾米  这是查莉
Amy, this is Charlie.
-很高兴认识你  -嗨
- Hi. Nice to meet you. - Hi, hi.
你是
And you are?
罗斯  以前跟你们住一个街区
Ross? I grew up on your block?
去年我们一起吃感恩节大餐
We had Thanksgiving together last year?
我和你姐生了个孩子
I had a baby with your sister?
不  我…
No. I....
昨天我从你那儿买了个沙拉三明治
Did I buy a falafel from you yesterday?
没错
Yes. Yes, you did.
瑞秋  你妹妹艾米来了
Hi, Rachel. Here's your sister Amy.
她说我应该胸肌整形
She thinks I need pec implants.
艾米  嗨
Amy? Hi.
-记得乔伊吗  -当然
- You remember Joey. - Yeah. Hey, sure.
-《我们的日子》里的演员  -对
- The Days of our Lives guy. - That's right, yeah.
你演得真烂
You are not good.
见到粉丝总是让人高兴
Always nice to meet a fan.
你来干嘛
So, now, what are you doing here?
我有大新闻
Well, I have huge news.
抱歉  等一下  我先看看孩子
Sorry, hold on. Let me check on the baby.
我有很重要的事  艾拉不能等等
This is important. Can't Ella wait?
她名叫"艾玛"
Her name is Emma.
干嘛改名呀
Why did you change it?
艾拉好听多了
Ella was so much prettier.
我哪晓得
What do I know?
我只是推着小车卖中东食品的罢了
I just sell Middle Eastern food from a cart.
你英文有长进
Hey, your English is getting better.
-天  -我知道
- Oh, my God. - I know.
她可能是我恨过的最辣的女孩
She may be the hottest girl I've ever hated.
你干嘛呢
What you working on?
莫妮卡和钱德勒的推荐信
Monica and Chandler's recommendation.
我想让文字透着机灵劲
I want it to sound smart,
但深奥的词我又不会
but I don't know any big words or anything.
那你试试"辞典"
Why don't you use your thesaurus?
我刚说了深奥的不会
What did I just say?
看着
Watch.
选中想改的词
Here, highlight the word you want to change,
在"工具"下面...
go under "tools" ...
找到"辞典"  它会"生成"... "给出"
...and the thesaurus generates-- Gives.
"给出"供选词语表
Gives a whole list of choices.
选一个听起来最有学问的词  就行了
You can pick the word that sounds smartest.
太好了  我变聪明了
My God, that's great. I'm smart.
不  我变得
No, no, I'm:
多智  伶俐  机敏  我爱这软件
"Brainy, bright, clever." I love this thing!
各位女士注意
Look out, ladies!
乔伊·崔比安尼重装上阵了
Joey Tribbiani's got the whole package!
天
God...
太美了
...so beautiful.
是啊  她好可爱
I know, isn't she?
不  我是说你的毯子
No, I was talking about your bedding.
艾米  你有啥新闻啊
All right, what's your news, Amy?
呃…
Well...
我要结婚了
...I'm getting married.
我的天
Wow! Oh, my God!
-和谁结婚  -一个男人
- To who? - This guy.
他的房子太牛了
He has a killer apartment.
-还有呢  -在第五大道
- And...? - And it's on Fifth.
电梯开门就到起居室
And the elevator opens up right into the living room.
-他人如何  -他还行
- No, what's he like? - Oh, he's okay.
还记得我以前的男朋友马克吗
Do you remember my old boyfriend Mark?
-记得  -就是他爸
- Yeah. - It's his dad.
-那他可…  -太老了  对
- Wow, so he's gotta be-- - Old? Yeah.
但他常常旅行
But he travels a lot,
不怎么呆在家
so he's hardly ever there.
亲爱的  不得不跟你说
Sweetie, I gotta tell you,
我怎么感觉你好象
it sounds a little bit like...
喜欢这房子胜过喜欢...
...you like the apartment more than you like--
米伦
Myron.
说过他年纪大嘛
Yeah, I told you he was old.
坐下
Sit down.
亲爱的  你知道的
Honey, you know...
我也曾差一点嫁个我不爱的人
...l once also almost married somebody that I didn't love.
-记得巴瑞吗  -记得他
- Do you remember Barry? - Remember him?
你睡了以后我们常亲热
God, we used to make out all the time after you went to sleep.
有时点头回答就够了
Sometimes just nodding is okay.
不管怎么样  听着
But anyway, listen.
没嫁给巴瑞  是我一生最英明的决定
Not marrying Barry was the best decision that I ever, ever made.
亲爱的  你应该得到真爱
Honey, Amy, you deserve true love.
你的另一半就在某处
Your soul mate is out there somewhere.
一个同龄人  聪明而有趣
Someone that is your age, that is smart, that is fun...
你也爱他在乎他
...and that you care about.
没错
You're right.
-没错  就这么干  -好
- You're right. I'm gonna do it. - Okay.
我要嫁给米伦
I'm gonna marry Myron
再接着找我的另一半
and keep looking for Mr. Right.
接着说吧
Okay, let's keep talking.
借过  我们过周年
Excuse me. Anniversary.
先生  请把玉米片挪挪
Sir, could you move your nachos?
这是我的位子
They're in my seat.
我们过周年
It's my anniversary.
到了
Here we are.
真不敢相信都一年了
I can't believe it's been a whole year.
是啊
I know.
这是最好的一年
This has been the best year....
我一辈子最快乐的一年
This has been the best year of my life!
同感
Me too!
从不知道会如此爱一个人
I never thought I could love someone this much!
同感
I feel the same way!
你慷慨  善良
You're so generous and kind,
而且在床上总是让我欲仙欲死
and you're amazing in bed!
我们在庆祝周年
It's our anniversary.
尼克斯的球迷们
Knicks fans, please turn your attention
请看记分板大屏幕这边
to the big screen on the scoreboard.
有人要问一个很特别的问题
Someone has a special question to ask.
老套  俗气  丢人现眼
How lame. It's so tacky and impersonal.
是吗
Really?
求婚最烂的招数
It's the worst way to propose.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
请看我写的推荐信
I finished my recommendation. Here.
你们看了一定会很高兴
And I think you'll be very, very happy.
从来没这么久盯着电脑
It's the longest I ever spent on a computer
居然没去看色情站的
without looking at porn.
看不懂
I don't understand.
有些词汇对于你来说太深奥了
Some of the words a little too sophisticated for you?
都讲不通啊
It doesn't make any sense.
怎么可能
Well, of course it does.
我写得很有学问的  我用的"辞典"
It's smart. I used a thesaurus.
每个词都用
On every word?
没错
Yep.
这句话原本是啥意思
All right, what was this sentence originally?
他们是慷慨热心的好人
"They are warm, nice people with big hearts."
结果变成
And that became,
他们是潮湿的  给人好感的智人
"They are humid, prepossessing Homo sapiens...
具有超额尺寸的心脏大动脉
...with full-sized aortic pumps."
是的  我真心这么想
Yeah. Yeah. And hey, I really mean it, dude.
乔伊  恐怕我们不能用这封信
All right, Joey, I don't think we can use this.
-为什么  -因为你的签名是
- Why not? - Well, because you signed it:
袋鼠宝宝  小崔
"Baby Kangaroo Tribbiani."
算了  你还是不要假装有学问
Why don't you stop worrying about sounding smart
就用你的本色来写怎么样
and just be yourself.
你不必用"辞典"   要用这里写
You don't need a thesaurus. Just write from here.
让它发自你超额尺寸的心脏大动脉
Your full-sized aortic pump.
-艾米  嗨  -我听了你的话
- Amy. Hi. - I took your advice.
-我跟米伦分手了  -太好了
- I left Myron. - Good for you!
是啊  我简直是艾琳·布洛科维奇
I know. I'm Erin Brockovich.
对
Yes, you are.
-以你为荣  -谢谢
- I'm so proud of you. - Thank you.
我能住你这里吗
So can I stay with you?
艾琳·布洛科维奇不是住她自己家吗
But Erin Brockovich had her own house.
看谁又来啦
Look who's back.
你怎么带行李
Why do you have bags?
瑞秋  她为什么带行李
Rach,why does she have bags?
我要和你们住一块了
I'm staying with you guys.
-什么  -我们成室友了
- What? - We're gonna be roomies!
来
Come on.
-你睡在外面  -是啊
- You slept out here? - Yeah.
她梦中总踢我
Amy kept kicking me in her sleep,
还嚷嚷  米伦  滚出去
yelling, "Myron, get off!"
我们会把她赶走对吧
But we're getting rid of her, right?
瑞秋  答应我  赶走她
Rachel,please tell me we're getting rid of her?
-我下不了手  乔伊  -噢  不会吧
- Joey, I can't do that. - Oh, come on.
昨晚我正在干光一个披萨
Last night I was finishing off a pizza,
她就说
and she said
嘴巴爽一秒  屁股胖一生
"A moment on the lips, forever on the hips."
在我家不需要这种屁话
I don't need that kind of talk in my house!
乔伊  我知道她难相处
Joey, look, I know that she's difficult...
但她来这里也不错
...but I think it's really good that she's here.
这样她滚蛋后我们才能更欢喜
Because we'll appreciate it more when she's gone?
不  只是  我刚来这城市的时候
No, it's just-- Look, when I first moved to this city,
还不是一样
I was a lot like her.
被惯坏  自我中心
I was spoiled, self-centered.
你们几个却照顾我
And you guys really took care of me.
莫妮卡强迫我们来着
Yeah. Monica made us.
不管怎样我都很感激
Well, whatever. I really appreciate it...
如果没有你们
...because I don't think I would be the person I am today...
也就没有现在的我
...if it wasn't for you guys.
我想帮帮艾米
So I want to help Amy
就像你们帮我那样
the way you guys helped me.
我知道这需要极大的耐性
And I know it's gonna take patience,
我可以
but that's okay.
-早  -早
- Good morning. - Yeah.
艾米  那是我今天要穿的衣服
That's what I'm wearing today.
所以我才挂在门上
That's why I hung it on the door.
宝贝  你总不能给我扒下来
Oh, sweetie, you can't pull this off.
你知道吗
You know what?
现在我们也许应当坐下来
I was thinking that maybe now would be a good time...
好好谈谈你的将来
...for us to sit down and, you know, talk about your future.
我没空
Oh, I can't, honey.
我要去修眉
I'm gonna go get my eyebrows shaped.
这样的眉毛像哭丧着脸
I am not happy.
你确定要吃吗
Sure you want to eat that?
我不就是丰满点吗  我喜欢
I'm curvy and I like it!
-嗨  -嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
最烂的周年庆
I just had the worst anniversary ever.
才不是呢
I doubt that.
给她讲讲我们去年怎么过的周年
Tell her about us last year.
我给钱德勒买了一只500块的表
Well, I bought Chandler a $500 watch,
而他  给我写了首饶舌歌
and he wrote me a rap song.
-真的  -用的办公软件
- Seriously? - Word.
我的比你还逊
Mine was worse than that.
怎么啦
Well, what happened?
球赛时
We were at the game.
有人在大屏幕上求婚
This guy proposed to his girlfriend on the big screen thing.
老套
That is so tacky.
我也是那么说
Well, that's what I said.
结果呢  原来迈克昨晚上就想用
But it turns out Mike was planning on
这种方式向我求婚
proposing to me the same way last night.
天  迈克要求婚
Oh, my God. Mike was gonna propose?
大件事
That's huge.
你想嫁他吗
Do you want to marry him?
当然想啦
Yeah, I really do. Yes.
结果我那句话把他堵回去了
But after I dumped on the way he was gonna do it...
我想他一辈子都不会求婚了
...l don't think he'll ever ask again.
在巴贝多斯我拒绝过他一次了  现在又一次
I said no in Barbados, and now this?
没错  如果我是男人
She's right. If I were a guy and....
我刚才是不是说  如果我是男人
Did I just say, "lf I were a guy"?
别等他求婚了
You don't need him to propose to you.
主动出击吧
Maybe you could propose to him.
哦  不知道
Oh, I don't know.
我又不是想嫁想疯了
I don't know. Isn't that a little desperate?
我向钱德勒求的婚
I proposed to Chandler.
好吧  继续讲
All right, moving on.
我不觉得你想嫁想疯了
I don't think it was desperate.
我觉得你很棒
It was amazing.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们都认为我该求婚
Well, do you think I should propose?
那一定很棒
I think it could be kind of great.
当然
Absolutely.
世上再没有比求婚
You'll love the feeling.
更美妙的感觉了
There's nothing like it.
好  那么以何种方式呢
Okay. Okay. So how should I do it?
就在球赛的大屏幕上啊
How about at a game on the big screen?
那去体育用品专卖店吧
How about at a Foot Locker?
他既然选择过大屏幕求婚
What? What, he obviously thinks
可见他能接受这种方式
that's a nice way to be proposed to.
而且他也不会起疑心
Plus, he'd never suspect it.
有理
Yeah, that does make sense.
你们会喜欢吗
Okay, now, would you two like that?
我喜欢
Sounds good to me.
不过男性会怎么想
But what would a guy think?
-奶奶电话  -哇
- Nana's on the phone. - Wow.
有趣
That's interesting,
她七年前就死了
since she died seven years ago.
是吗
She did?
那她在博卡的房子归谁了
Who got her condo in Boca?
喂
Hello?
是我们的保姆
It's our nanny.
喂
Hi.
是吗  希望你早点康复  再见
Oh, God, I hope you feel better. Okay. Bye.
是莫利  她病了
That's Molly. She's sick.
今天你看艾玛可以吗
Can you watch Emma today?
不行  我要连堂上课
I can't. I have back-to-back classes.
莫利说她生什么病
Did Molly say what she had?
我的喉咙也不舒服
Because my throat's been hurting.
痛经
Menstrual cramps.
我可能不是这毛病
I don't think that's what this is.
你们帮忙看着艾玛成吗
Can any of you watch Emma?
抱歉  亲爱的
No, I'm sorry, sweetie.
我要上班  还要求婚
No, I've got work, and then I'm proposing.
糟糕  那怎么办
Great. Shoot. What am I gonna do?
我可以帮忙
Well, I could do it.
好  实际上...
Well, actually....
能跟你说句话吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
我不想让她看我们的孩子
I do not want her babysitting our child.
为啥
Why not?
首先  她老是把我们的孩子喊成"艾拉"
For one thing, she keeps calling her Ella.
这名字也不错嘛
Ella's a nice name.
好  下一胎叫"艾拉"
Fine, we'll call the next one Ella.
-下一胎  -好
- The next one? - Okay.
我不赞成她帮我们看孩子
I don't want her watching our baby.
我只是想改造她
Ross, I am trying to help her become a better person.
这是个好机会
This is a huge breakthrough for her.
她刚刚主动要求
She just offered to do something
帮助别的人类了
for another human being.
我不确定
You know, I don't know.
罗斯  我是说
Ross, I'm telling you...
她宁愿牺牲修眉的时间看孩子
...she's giving up getting her eyebrows shaped to do this, all right?
你知道这件事
Do you understand
对我们女人来说牺牲多重大吗
how important that is in our world?
我不小心听到你们的谈话
Listen, I couldn't help but overhear,
因为我想听
because I was trying to.
就让我带孩子吧
Listen, let me do this.
我真心想帮你们
I really want to help you guys out.
而且  瑞秋对我太好了
And plus, Rachel's been so wonderful to me.
-好  -太好了
- Absolutely. - Oh, great!
付多少工钱
So how much does it pay?
乔伊
Hi,Joe.
二稿如何
How's the second draft of the letter coming?
很好  我已经写完了
Great. I'm finished.
实际上  我已经交了
In fact, I just dropped it off at the agency.
-交了  -是啊
- You dropped it off? - Yeah.
我们能读读吗
Can we read it?
能再打印一份给我们吗
Can you print out another copy?
恐怕不行啊  朋友
No can do, amigo.
没用电脑
No, I didn't use the computer.
手写的  显得更亲切
It felt more personal to handwrite it.
-还手写  -别担心
- You handwrote it? - Yeah, and don't worry.
我根本没有装聪明
I didn't try to sound smart at all.
再见
See you later.
我的天  我的天
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
那信会放入我们的档案里
That letter is gonna go in our file.
我们这辈子别想有孩子了
We're never gonna get a kid.
我们会孤独终老
We're gonna be one of those old couples...
养花弄鸟
...that collects orchids or has a lot of birds.
没事的
It's okay. You know what?
我打电话给领养中心
I will just call the agency
请他们扔掉那封信
and tell them to throw out the letter.
好
Okay, good.
喂  我是钱德勒·宾
Hello, this is Chandler Bing.
有人手写了
Someone just dropped off
一封推荐信
a handwritten recommendation letter and....
好
Okay.
谢谢  再见
Thank you. Goodbye.
我们完蛋了  是不是
We're screwed, aren't we?
这样吧
You know what?
买鸟的路上说给我听
Just tell me on the way to the bird store.
-他们喜欢那封信  -什么
- They loved it. - What?
他们说我们很聪明
They thought it was very smart of us
叫个小孩写推荐信
to have a child write the letter.
他们以为乔伊是小孩
They thought Joey was a child?
她看了他的画  以为他只八九岁
She guessed 8, 9, based on his drawings.
-嗨  -嗨  你们今天干嘛了
- Hi. - Hey, what'd you guys do today?
艾拉想上街
Ella wanted to go out,
所以我们去购物  还吃了寿司
so we went shopping and got some sushi.
-有趣  -也不是啦
- That sounds like fun. - Yeah, not really.
婴儿都好无趣
Babies are dull.
-我家小妹妹怎样了  -我很好
- Hey. Hi, how's my girl? - I'm fine.
我准备送你礼物
And I got you a present
来谢谢你留我住
for letting me stay with you.
-准备好了  -嗯
- Ready? - Yeah.
你给她穿了耳洞
You pierced her ears?
她的鼻子看来小点了吗
Doesn't it make her nose look smaller?
你给她穿了耳洞
You pierced her ears?
竟然不征求我同意
How could you do this without telling me?
我若先告诉你
If I had told you,
就不是惊喜了
then it wouldn't have been a surprise, now would it?
我觉得她看来很可爱
I think she looks cute.
但我错了
But I am wrong.
我的天啊  罗斯来了
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Here comes Ross.
罗斯会发飚的
He's gonna flip out.
为什么  他卖三明治的推车
Why, did something happen
让城管收了吗
to his falafel cart?
-嗨  各位  -罗斯
- Hey, guys. - Ross!
嗨  艾玛
Hi, Emma.
她的帽子干嘛压这么低
Why is she wearing her hat so low?
她都看不见了
She can barely see.
人家不想她看见嘛
I don't really want her to see.
为啥
Why not?
世界太可怕
Because there are so many terrible sights in this world.
有战争  还有乔伊冰箱里那玩意儿
Like war. Or that thing in Joey's refrigerator. Remember?
一只牛奶盒  但看来像块肉
It was in a milk carton, but it looked like meat?
快来
Come here.
看她多乖
There she is. Hi.
-怎么啦  -没啥
- What? - Nothing.
嗨
Hi.
什么
What--?
那是夹上去的吧
Please tell me those are clip-ons!
是扎的耳洞
Oh, they're real.
是她干的
Did she do this to her?
我早说过
I told you
不能把艾玛交到她手上
we shouldn't have left Emma with her!
我知道了  你说得对
I know, I know. And you were right, Ross.
你太不负责
Okay? You are so irresponsible!
绝不再让你看孩子
I am never letting you babysit again!
你们知道吗  她需要我
You know what? This kid needs me, okay?
她需要一个又酷又有趣的阿姨
She needs to have a cool, fun aunt.
我就是
I'm a cool, fun aunt.
好吧
Okay.
莫妮本来就是又酷又有趣
Hey! Monica can be cool and fun
而且有条有理
at organized indoor projects.
我只不过想帮你
All I wanted to do was help you
想清楚你将来想干什么
try to figure out what to do with your life.
结果呢  你还是小孩子
This is how you repay me?
谁稀罕你帮忙
I don't need you to help me.
我自己早想好我的人生要干什么了
Because I already know what I'm gonna do with my life.
-是吗  几时想好的  -今天
- Oh, yeah? Since when? - Since today.
我要当婴儿时尚专家
I am going to be a baby stylist.
-啊  -有这职业吗
- What? - That's not a thing!
该有
Well, it should be.
我要教婴儿如何配饰
I'm gonna help babies learn how to accessorize...
选衣裳的颜色
...what colors to wear,
什么衣服较瘦身
what clothes are slimming.
婴儿才不管苗条不苗条
Babies don't care if they're slim!
如何像艾米一样美
Enter Amy.
艾米  我要…
Amy, l-- I just-- I just wanna--
你想怎样
What? What are you gonna do?
罚你永世没有三明治吃
No more falafel for you!
比赛很精彩
Great game, huh?
你怎么老瞄大屏幕
Why do you keep looking at the screen?
没  我在祷告
I'm not. I'm praying.
请让尼克斯队赢吧
Please let the Knicks win.
谢谢你  雷神
Thank you, Thor.
你上哪儿
Where are you going?
嘘嘘去
I'm going to the bathroom.
等一会
Well, I think you should wait.
为啥
Why?
如果不憋一会
Well, if you don't hold it in,
你就无法摄取所有养分
you don't get all the nutrients.
尼克斯球迷
Knicks fans, please turn your attention
请注意记分牌大屏幕
to the big screen on the scoreboard.
有人要问特别的问题
Someone has a special question to ask.
迈克·汉尼根  我们结婚吧
Mike Hannigan, will you marry me?
看啊  女人向男人求婚
Get a load of this. She's proposing to him!
我们知道谁是爷们了
Guess we know who wears the pants in that family.
不要误导观众
Well, that's not very enlightened.
不许嘘我们
Boo us? Boo you!
喂  我就是乔伊·崔比安尼
Hello? Yeah, this is Joey Tribbiani.
哦  嗨
Oh, hi.
真高兴你喜欢我的信
Well, I'm glad you liked my letter.
不  我爸妈不在家
No, my mommy and daddy aren't home right now.
再见
Okay, bye-bye.
这人真好
She was nice.
乔伊  把艾米的箱子拿出来  她要搬走了
Joey, get Amy's bags. She is moving out.
你要把我赶出去
You're kicking me out?
你给我的女儿穿耳洞
You put holes in my baby's ears.
不然大家怎么知道她是女孩
At least now people will know she's a girl!
不敢相信  我竟然想过要帮你
I can't believe I ever even tried to help you.
-你不可救药  -你知道吗
- You are so beyond help! - You know what?
这次见面你在否定我的一切
Ever since I got here, you have been nothing but negative.
-你说什么  -你不准我…
- Excuse me? - You didn't want me...
嫁有豪宅的老头
...to marry the old guy with the great apartment.
我想帮你把你女儿的鼻子变小点
Then I tried to help your daughter de-emphasize her flaws...
结果吃力不讨好
...and suddenly I'm the bad guy?
乔伊  行李怎么还没搬出来
Joey, where are those bags?
她的破玩意太多了
She has a lot of crap!
我刚搬来时
You know? When I moved in here,
还憧憬姐妹团聚
I thought, "This will be so great.
像童年那样
Just us sisters back together again like when we were kids."
而且没有该死的吉尔捣乱
Except without that stupid Jill.
她变肥了
Who has gotten fat, by the way.
真的
Seriously?
妈说吉尔肥了15磅
Mom said she gained, like, 15 pounds.
-屁股和大腿长肉了  -屁股和脸
- Hips or thighs? - Ass and face.
天啊  她不是节食吗
Oh, my God! I thought she was on Atkins.
本来是  但是还是没能抵挡碳水化合物的诱惑
She was. Carbs found her.
看  这才像姐妹
See? This is what I wanted.
真心交谈
Two sisters talking about real stuff.
哦  我可以这样
Oh, I can give you that.
-你可以  -是的
- You can? - Yeah.
我老想改造你  实际上
I kept trying to make you a better person, but you're....
你本来就接近完美了
You're already a pretty perfect version of what you are.
谢谢你
Thank you.
必须承认  艾玛真可爱
You gotta admit, Emma does look cute.
你刚说"艾玛"
Did you just say, "Emma"?
对不起  艾拉
Oh, I'm sorry. Ella.
赛场里那女人真是乱讲
That woman didn't know what she was talking about, Mike.
你当然有种
Obviously, you have balls.
忘了算了
Please, let's forget the whole thing.
你能忘最好
I would love it.
已经忘了
Consider it forgotten.
谢谢
Thank you.
但是我要你知道
But just so you know....
不管你何时以何方式求婚
However and whenever you decide to propose,
我保证都答应
I promise I'll say yes.
不管是篮球赛
Whether, you know, it's at a basketball game...
还是用飞机在空中拉条幅
...or in skywriting...
或是像一些滥电影里
...or, you know, like some lame guy in a cheesy movie...
把求婚戒指藏在蛋糕里
...who hides it in the cake.
藏蛋糕里了  对吧
It's in the cake, isn't it?
没种的男人还会有什么好点子吗
Where else would lame Mr. No Balls hide it?
老是毁坏你的一番美意
What's the matter with me?
怎么老提这个
Why do I keep ruining this?
对不起  真对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
是我错
No, it's my fault.
我老用愚蠢的方式求婚
I keep trying to propose in these stupid ways...
我只是想告诉你  我爱你
...and I just wanna tell you I love you,
我想和你过余生
and I wanna spend my life with you....
我现在求婚
I'm gonna do this now.
天啊
Oh, my God.
菲比
Phoebe, l--
等等
Wait. Oh, wait.
Oh, no.
好了
Okay.
可以了
Ready? Okay.
菲比  我爱你
Phoebe, I love you.
世界上没一个女人
There's no one else in the world
能让我费尽心机来求三次婚
I would ask to marry me three times.
我想照顾你
But I want to take care of you...
和你生儿育女
...have babies with you...
一起变老
...and grow old with you.
菲比·布菲  你愿意嫁我吗
Phoebe Buffay, will you marry me?
我愿意
Yes.
-我爱你  -我爱你更多
- I love you. - I love you more.
不可能
Not possible.
她是"没种夫人"了
She's gonna be Mrs. No Balls!
婴儿时尚专家的事情怎么样了
So how's the baby-styling business going?
行情不大好
Not that great.
好象大家都不爱听
It's almost as if people don't want
别人说他家的孩子丑
to hear that their babies are ugly.
还有这事儿
That's shocking.
那不是罗斯吗  罗斯
There's Ross. Hey, Ross.
你好  罗斯
Hello, Ross?
真没教养
He's rude.